All right. Um, but taking a look at the
markets, it's a complete U-turn is what
both the benchmark indices have taken
right now. But shifting focus to the
insurance space then as we have the
August provisional general insurance
data. How have the industry leaders um
and others players have flared in the
month of August. Anorag is here with a
roundup. Anorag. So in month of August
as per the provisional figure as per our
sources the general insurance industry
has seen a degrowth of minus 15%. So
month-on-month figure as compared to
July uh uh 2025 to August 2025
uh Go Digit has seen a degus 16%, ic
Lombard has seen a degus
12%. Uh New India Assurance
growth in premium in comparison to July
in August is of minus 47%.
Standalone health insurance company Neva
Bupa has also seen a degrowth of minus
uh 3.8%
and star health insurance has seen a
degrowth of minus 6%. So not a good
month for general insurance industry.
I'll go through uh yearon-year number
also also there is a catch in
yearon-year number that last year the
long-term premium was allowed but from
1st of October the long-term premium is
not allowed. So that is a catch but in a
long-term yearon-year numbers uh
industry has grown up by 4.2% as
compared to last year. ICIC Lombard has
grown by 2%. New India Assurance has
shown a growth of uh 9% as compared to
last year August 2024. Go Digit has
shown a growth of 13.5% as compared uh
to last year August 2024. uh similarly
nabupa and star health was also shown a
growth of uh 2% nabupa 2.74% and star
health 1.85% 85%. So not a good month
for general insurance industry. The
August provisional data is showing a
degrowth in uh general insurance
industry.
>> So concern in the general insurance
industry and that was a quick round up
the August scorecard. Thanks for that.